bizshark.com 2009-03-06

# BizShark Privacy Policy

BizShark Business Search (or BizShark.com) respects the privacy of all users and visitors. This privacy policy discloses any information that we collect, use, and share about our users and visitors. BizShark reserves the right to modify this policy at any time without prior notice. Any modification to this policy will be updated here.

1\. Collection of Site Visitor Information

BizShark uses cookies to help deliver a personalized user experience. We may collect IP addresses, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and other traffic data for aggregated system analysis. We do not collect any personally identifiable information from our visitors.

2\. Collection of Premium Member Information

When BizShark premium members sign up for a subscription, they must enter a valid credit card and/or other payment information needed to process their payments. BizShark does not store or process any credit card information. Instead, we employ an independent and reputable payment processor to ensure the highest security standards.

During the sign-up process, BizShark will also collect personally identifiable information that includes name and email address. We use this information to process registrations, maintain premium accounts, send important account notifications, and complement our services. All member information is kept private and secure.

3\. Information Disclosure

BizShark may need to share your information with third-party service providers to help improve the service. We may disclose personally identifiable information if required to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

4\. Change of Ownership

In the event of a merger, acquisition, or a sale to another company, your information may be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer. BizShark will notify our users about any change of ownership via email or a public notice on the Site.

5\. Contact Us

For more information in regards to this privacy policy, please email us at privacy[at]bizshark.com.
